There is a threat to me-
On a social media channel,
belonging to ISIS.
But I'm not afraid.
As we say in Raqqa:
Death is death.
Try to relax if you can.
-We always do that.
After a long working day, we are enjoying ourselves
in the evening. Especially here in New York.
Congratulations.
-Thanks.
Thanks for what you do. Worldwide
will be inspired by your efforts.
Fight on.
-Thanks.
These are the guys from Raqqa.
The situation is difficult everywhere.
-Definitely.
Some situations are terrible,
but others are even more terrible.
Fantastic.
May I have a little smile?
You are so serious, my friend.
Everyone here can mention
true journalistic heroes.
The men and women in Raqqa Become
Slaughtered in silence stands out.
They all work secretly-
-to report on ISIS '
demolitions in their hometown.
Some have fled
for fear of their lives, -
-self in exile
are they by no means safe.
It is with great humility, -
-I'm overriding
Press Release Prize 2015-
to the brave men and women in
Raqqa Be Slammed In Silence.
This is the story of Raqqa, -
Our forgotten Syrian city
by the river Euphrates, -
-which is now known
as the main city of Islamic State.
And that has become a ghost town.
But for us it was
and will always be our home.
RAQQA, SYRIEN
Raqqa was a simple and secluded city.
My city's inhabitants are known
for their generosity and sacrifice.
Weddings can last for days.
When a house on the street was happy,
happiness spread throughout the neighborhood.
Life was quite normal for us.
But then everything changed.
After 40 years under the Assad regime
we began to shout for freedom.
What do we want?
-Freedom!
Assad, your liar, freedom is near.
Travel now, Assad.
Travel, Assad!
Syria created headlines
in the Arab spring
-with a sadness,
That had never been expressed before.
A bunch of school boys
made graffiti on a school wall.
The people want the regime to fall.
They were arrested and tortured.
15 boys were sparked,
that sparked all Syria.
Raqqa
MARCH 2012
Get him away!
I did not expect to attend
in the rebellion against the Assad regime.
I was just a student
and not even politically active.
My evenings went along
to fix and make trouble
But I quickly grew up.
The Syrian rebellion changed us.
AZIZ
SPOKESMAN
I taught in high school.
While I was teaching,
one of my students was arrested.
I could not tie anymore.
A oppressed people make rebellion and desires
freedom, justice and equality.
Hopefully, we'll finally win.
I was inverted. A juniper.
I was obsessed with filming.
I used to film almost everything.
Hamoud
CAMERA MAN
This is the city of Raqqa.
Here are the streets of the Euphrates.
My father was afraid of me.
He said:
Stay out of journalism, you see
not hit by a wild sphere.
But danger is tempting.
So I filmed the rebels,
who fought against Assad.
It is the first province,
Being freed from Assad's regime.
That's how tyrants fall.
THE 5 JULY 2014
ABU BAKR AL-BAGHDADI
LEADERS OF ISIS
Promised to be the prophet
and his followers and his soldiers.
Your brothers in battle were blessed
with victory and achievements.
So we exclaimed a caliphate.
A paradise where the rivers run
in the garden of Eden.
It is God's will.
Raqqa
JULY 2014
In the power room after the rebellion
took a new group of Raqqa.
Its members held a black flag
and called the Islamic State.
We filmed them in secret,
when they arrived.
And we filmed them when they asked people
to gather at the Freedom Square.
Tyran Assad's crimes-
-was worse for every day
But now is the Islamic state
in Iraq and the Levant here.
Islamic State almost declines
Instantly Raqqa from the outside world.
Only news from the city was propaganda
from the so-called Islamic state.
You are part of prophecy.
Allah has chosen your destiny.
We have proclaimed a new caliphate.
Stay with them,
That follows the religion of Allah.
Join us!
Before we force you.
Join the believers,
before the punishment of God hits you.
Cry!
-God is great!
At first glance
resembled the other militant groups.
But we soon realized that the world never
had seen the stomach of this group.
They painted the city black
and wrapped it in the dark.
We could not help
while Raqqa was slaughtered in silence.
Are you playing?
-Yes.
DOWN WITH ISIS
At that point the goal was to wake up
the attention of the local authorities.
But the situation was getting worse soon.
Executions and detentions
took place interchangeably.
Nothing was reported in Arabic
or international media.
We had to do something with more power.
We had to get our city in the spotlight-
-and show people the truth about ISIS,
and what was happening in Raqqa.
It was RBBS 'first call.
Raqqa Be Slammed In Silence
We created a page on Facebook-
- and began to post in english
via Twitter, -
so the civil voices could be
heard by the international community.
Sir. Naji, they have graduated hundreds
by civil journalists. Tell about it.
He is the protagonist and activist.
Near the window.
What has happened in Syria,
is true civil journalism.
Naji Jerf, called Uncle,
is the campaign's father figure.
He educated us as civilians
journalists to show us
-The pen is stronger
than the sword.
And day by day our work became
discovered on Arab channels.
The campaign Raqqa Becomes Slaughtered
in silence is initiated by students.
These young men will show the world,
what happens in their province.
ISIS detained at least 1200
and committed many massacres in the city.
We pierced the hole in the dark.
Public executions
at Raqqa's former Paradise Square.
ISIS 'enemies are being killed here,
and their bodies will be exhibited.
ISIS responded strongly to the campaign.
People asked:What is
Raqqa Be Slammed In Silence ?
God, freeze the blood to the ice in their veins!
And stand your breath, sir!
Do they have to burn in your graves!
It lasted only a couple of weeks,
and then hit the tragedy.
It is a very old ID.
It's a fake id.
No, I swear by God.
But it's torn apart here.
It is false.
Our friend Moutaz was detained
at a checkpoint.
Are you playing?
He was arrested and jailed.
After they had tortured him,
did they examine his laptop-
- and found information
and the movement logo.
They tortured him further
and asked:
Who are they? What are you working on?
You are against Islamic State.
In God the Name of Mercy. The penalty
for those who fight for god ...
After they shot Moutaz,
began a series of assassinations.
When the rescue service arrived,
Could they just carry Fare Hamadi?
and Ibrahim Abdel Qaders lay out.
They were members of a group,
that puts life at risk
-to tell the world what
It happens in their hometown, Raqqa.
They were both beheaded.
We had two options.
Staying in town
and see death in your eyes or travel.
So we decided
to flee from Raqqa.
Some of us fled
to Germany,-
the others were right on
the other side of the border in Turkey.
And then the real war began
between ISIS and us.
GAZIANTEP, TURKEY
RBSS-HAVEN
I had never considered
to leave Raqqa.
But I had no choice.
Even though we are outside,
we are still trying to fight
the world's most dangerous organization.
It is our source in Raqqa.
Yes, Ibrahim. Hello?
Right now, the situation is in Raqqa
worse than ever.
ISIS takes ...
Ibrahim? Hello?
What's the story about?
-Tre air attacks.
The source may send us more news,
which we can post in a couple of hours.
Have you got pictures and videos?
-Not yet.
The Internet in Raqqa
is very bad.
Uploading files takes a long time.
We may not get the videos this evening.
There is no injured person.
You have a problem with the accents.
-You must teach me the accents.
I broke from the school hours.
Therefore he became a math teacher.
-I am a math cooker.
Ask me about prime numbers and that kind of.
Ask me about verse, grammar etc.
I do not want to deal with that.
Do you want to teach again?
-If I find children, I teach them.
My dream is to get married,
before I die
We'll get you married.
I'm not optimistic.
-You'll get married.
yes you love her
you love her
She lives alone without you
We live all the time
on flight from ISIS.
Even though we have changed address often,
ISIS has collected information about us.
They post pictures with our names
and photographs of where we live.
I liked your entrance.
I look forward to seeing you again.
GERMANY
We can lose one of us every moment.
I was so lucky
to come to Germany.
But I feel guilty, -
Because of many of the others
Still in Turkey or Syria.
RBSS-HAVEN
A SECRETARY PLACE IN GERMANY
My brother lived in Raqqa, -
-and he sent me information.
He could not stay there anymore -
Then he decided to travel.
He brought a boat
Like all the other Syrians.
All those who flee from the war.
And he died in the sea.
If I sometimes like
will send him a message, -
I send it to him on Facebook.
Maybe he wants it.
I miss you, Mousa.
My brother, I'm broken.
Perfect. Okay.
Aziz, how is life in Raqqa today?
The life of Raqqa.
There is no life in Raqqa.
ISIS has limited
all aspects of life.
There are no schools,
universities or hospitals.
Sometimes there is no power
for three to four days or a whole week.
That's the problem. The situation
makes many people join the ISIS.
Many wonder,
how are you financed?
We all come
from middle class families, -
so we funded ourselves
in the first nine months.
Then we got support from NGOs.
-Okay.
You show your faces.
Are you not afraid they find you?
The Islamic State, our country,
is here to stay.
These spies and them,
there came before them
-inflicted Islamic state's right.
Do we know them?
We tell you,
that you will lose the war.
But when you lose this time,
Your children will inherit your defeat
and remember you as they fool
-thought
they could fight the Islamic state.
God cursed them.
RAQQA, SYRIEN
We consist of two teams.
The inner group is in Raqqa-
and consists of
about 17 correspondents.
ISIS 'MAIN QUARTER
The task of the inner group is
to film, photograph-
- and deliver important news.
In God's name,
it's Raqqa's soup cookie.
The task of the external group is
to communicate with the team in there.
Rashidi, go to the door.
A girl will bring something to you.
She has a dark red scarf on.
The inner group
then sends us information.
There is a major air attack to the north.
From our correspondent in Ain Issa.
Should I send it to you,
so you can post it?
Then we get in the outer group
it out in the world.
The clip is ready.
I'm putting it online now.
ISIS 'propaganda images
shows a quiet city.
The warriors boast of
to enjoy their imported food.
But these pictures show something else
according to activists in Raqqa.
Children stand in line at a supper kitchen.
Lack of food and high inflation.
Hospitals lack supplies.
So terrible is life
in ISIS 'stronghold.
LIVING IN RAQQA IS A MARRIAGE
Maybe we can not change it,
it happens,-
-but we can put pressure
on the authorities.
Hopefully
will our campaign win?
and one day we can
return to the city.
During the rebellion against Assad-
I did
to edit images and videos.
In my opinion, have a camera
more power than one weapon.
Therefore,
That keeps the camera stronger.
When ISIS came to Raqqa, -
-were they spread their decrees
via CDs.
The videos were
very badly made-
- and so forth,
as if they were filmed with phones.
But then ISIS decided to work
more on their media than weapons.
Then all movies after the takeover
of Raqqa is professionally made-
to recruit people
to their paradise.
For Allah's sake.
FOR ALLAH'S OBJECTIVE
WILL WE MARCH
TO PARADISE'S PORT
WHERE OUR YEAR FRUITS WAIT
The state has a large lack of men-
-with good media skills,
so the people can get the right news.
Major productions
with Hollywood techniques, -
-like comparable to movies
with high production value.
Whatever the video is about -
- Always with the same effects
and the same professionalism-
-to attract supporters
Like the known game
Grand Theft Auto.
Why play it on the computer,
when you can do it in reality?
It's the media war,
as ISIS now leads-
to recruit people
to their so-called Islamic state.
But ISIS does not represent
Islam, I know.
They exploit Islam
for personal gain-
-and uses videos to do that.
After my father's video was posted,
I did not notice the effects.
I only noticed,
what eventually happened.
Two months after
we started the campaign ...
... promised ISIS a bounty for killing
on me or information about me
When ISIS realized,
that they could not get hold of me
Did they keep my dad?
I watch the video tit.
It gives me strength.
I'm the father of the refugee
Hamoud Al-Moussa, -
-which fights the Islamic state.
I advise all fathers
to keep an eye on your sons.
HASSAN
HAMOUDS BROR
We are Muslims and believe in
that he has come to heaven
Praise be to God.
When I get angry I bleed.
-Are you okay?
I think ...
I do not know.
It's our oldest brother, Ahmed.
Two weeks ago we were told that
that ISIS had also executed him.
They executed our brother and father
to make us stop.
But we will continue.
I promise you we will continue.
RAQQA, SYRIEN
Since our campaign began,
ISIS has gone to extreme lengths-
-to prevent our members from
to work in Raqqa.
They set checkpoints
and investigates people and phones-
-the pursuit of recording equipment.
It's almost impossible
to get information out of Raqqa.
RAQQA 12
RBSS correspondent
ISIS abducts, kills
and just make people disappear.
All they designate
to be media activists.
They track everything we do.
Each photo and every video we post.
They are always trying to catch us.
We use satellite internet, -
But ISIS tracks the signal
with cars that drive around.
So you can only be in a short time, -
- and during that time one must
encrypt and send the information.
We have learned from the mistakes,
we did with Moutaz, -
because he had RBSS material
when he was caught.
Once the information has been sent,
they are deleted from the group's equipment.
I'm in the room.
The outer group has a department, -
- hiding information about people,
There may be danger.
To protect our reporter-
We upload the material
at the right time.
Our correspondents,
Who works in Raqqa, -
-it is them,
history should be written.
I definitely agree,
that I can be killed
But the most important thing for me is,
that the campaign does not stop.
This is our message to ISIS.
If you think the killing of three
or four members of the campaign-
-will stop the campaign,
then you're wrong.
The murders and slaughter,
that takes place in the city.
The hardships people live with.
Poverty, hunger and disease.
ISIS prevents people from leaving
city ??and use them as shields.
Such is the situation
in Raqqa's quarreled city.
GAZIANTEP, TURKEY
Yes, Ibrahim. How are you?
It was a long time ago.
-Yes, where have you been?
I can hear you.
Hello?
-How is the situation at Ain Issa?
ISIS arrived at six o'clock in the morning.
We could hear them shouting.
At the morning prayer you could hear
the girls scream. They probably became obscene.
I've heard that ISIS too
has taken the Al-Kadrieh area.
Is that right? Write it down here.
I'm not sure. I know,
that there are violent clashes.
How many ISIS soldiers
have almost been killed?
Between 20 and 40 ISIS soldiers, -
-but the resistance movement
has lost over 100 people.
I can go to Raqqa
and get more information.
It is enough.
No no, do not put your life at risk.
Well. God bless you.
God bless you. Take care of yourself.
Put it up.
ANGREB ON RAQQA
AND ISIS OBJECTIVES IN AIN ISSA
Raqqa is slaughtered in silence
without the media's attention.
This campaign is a response
on the great silence.
Videos that have been smuggled
out of ISIS 'high castle, -
- is the only insight into life
under the extremist regime.
Videos that will charge ISIS
and disprove ISIS 'claims about, -
-to the so-called Islamic state
is prosperous and well functioning.
We not only report news.
Sometimes we do
awareness campaigns.
We have a magazine called Dabba.
It has the same front page
like ISIS 'magazine, -
-but when we open ours,
it is discovered that it is against ISIS.
It drove ISIS to madness.
Hello? Hello?
Yes, is everything okay?
I can not hear you.
You fall out.
Journalist Naji Jerf has become
murdered in Gaziantep in Turkey.
According to sources he was murdered
because of resistance to Assad and ISIS.
Naji Jerf was shot
at high light day-
on a busy street in the south
Turkey near the Syrian border.
Jerf worked with the group
Raqqa Be Slammed In Silence.
Naji ...
You deserve joy.
You deserve everything well.
You deserve Syria.
You deserve those who love you.
You deserve freedom, Naji.
There are no gods other than Allah!
Allah loves the martyr!
We lost part of the campaign.
A close friend of the group.
And the fact that,
that he was murdered in Turkey,
Come as a shock to us.
Yes, Aziz.
Yes. We must go away from here.
Yes, really.
The way they murdered Naji
inside the middle of town.
I can not stay here anymore.
We have the knife for the throat.
I have to get my wife out.
See you soon if God will.
Rose?
You know what?
It's a good apartment
to see Germany.
It's as if we should
on honeymoon there.
-It's a set more.
-The nice clothes
We must see when we get it on.
We have bought it in vain.
Is there any more?
-No.
Take care of yourself.
It will be OK.
Be strong.
We are talking to Yaqoub.
RBSS-HAVEN
RAQQA, SYRIEN
There has just been news from Raqqa.
They just got to know
that ISIS prohibits satellite dishes.
My Goodness.
They have put the posters up today.
The mobile signal is weak as usual.
Here is the poster. It explains that,
Why people should destroy the parabolic.
Write that he should be careful.
-I have done that.
Hello.
I have pictures and a poster
about the ban on parabolas.
ISIS has set it up today.
I send them,
so you can put them up.
ISIS isolates Raqqa from the outside world.
ISIS is losing media war.
They have closed internet cafes
and prohibited televisions and satellite dishes.
They limit people's lives
in Raqqa strongly.
Especially for our correspondents.
Try to stop it
to send information from Raqqa.
So we decided
fight against the street level.
How to get to ISIS.
Syria is free. Quit with ISIS
There is no ISIS, there is no Assad.
Freedom forever.
Where is he
RBSS-HAVEN
A SECRETARY PLACE IN GERMANY
Ever since Allah has created Adam,
Was there a war?
between believers and unbelievers.
Between the truth and the lies,
between good and evil.
This war took over
many ways, -
-and one of them is the media war.
In journalists,
that fight Islam and its state-
-with the tongues and feathers.
Your journalistic work
it does not protect it.
Stop fighting otherwise
Do you like the sort of them?
-which was shot in silence
of the soldiers of the caliphate.
Killed silent
-Is it a fee?
It's Naji,
And to the right is Ibrahim.
And do not think you're protected
for being in europe
A sharp knife
or a bullet in the head
it will be your destiny
Members of the pig.
GAZIANTEP, TURKEY
He could not sleep at night.
I put the light wave and thought:
What will be next?
Sarmad is being killed
and then Aghiad, Hassan and Mohamad.
And what then?
I figured he was
An island and lost someone every day.
You think there will be
probably in germany
There will be ...
Without a doubt, sure?
They can reach us all over the world.
You are constantly worried
-Yes, my nerves are thin.
One begins to wait,
who dies for natural causes.
GERMANY
Fear started
spread between us.
After Naji's murder we got it
to be shown by the German government.
We must have members
by the group one by one.
But there may be
There are no safe places in the world for us.
How are you?
I'm glad you were sure.
Probably go.
It's all right, Sarmad.
I feel like someone else,
after leaving Istanbul.
Well, you're not too wild.
Big Berlin, Aziz?
-Cmpedor.
Almost as big as Istanbul.
-It's true?
And you want to see people,
There is a full day.
This is what you see here.
Europe has open cities.
They do not have taboos
God help us. They are without judgment.
Everything is modern and new.
We give you a frantic means.
I hope not
We just gave him five euros.
We will live our lives here.
We can create a home.
Having a son,
And you will get citizenship.
Do not feel good
-Now.
Hello, Sfef. How do you feel
It scared me
Let's go
You started
to go through the streets.
Not me
Defend yourself! Defend yourself!
Even your snow is different.
We take farewell farewell farewell.
We are out of Berlin.
There is snow everywhere in Germany.
My wife loves winter,
but I can not.
I hate the winter and the cold.
As I expected the houses to look like.
I hope that our appearance looks like this.
I like those houses.
I do not care if it's good.
I just want a house.
RBSS-HAVEN
A SECRETARY PLACE IN GERMANY
Hassan
HAMOUDS BROR
In the last semester of the year,
Death was the time?
the most common in my life.
But I'm glad that Hassan
he joined me in Germany.
And I try to be stronger.
Because my life is changing.
Soon I will be my father.
He is a boy.
It is a great responsibility.
I hope you have a better life,
than we have
Because we only saw bad things.
We ascend into a world of war.
We rise up in a rebellion.
Our lives have been destroyed.
The least I can do is
to ensure my child a future.
Because I can not
Be alive in a year or two.
I do not want my son to go
I feel like I do without a father
This is our message:
We are the lions of Califato.
We follow the path of holy wars.
We do not put our arms before
We can win or become martyrs.
Children are firewood from ISIS.
Like other extremist groups,
-using ISIS children
In the war against your enemies.
In accordance with the rules of combat of ISIS requires
all combat suicides.
The majority are children who screamed
and he is not afraid of death.
God is great.
Shout
-Good is great.
These caliphate fields
It is now in all besieged cities, -
where children wash their brain every day
The Islamic state arrived!
-The Islamic state has arrived!
Even the streets became
converted into fields
I'm not afraid not only,
that my children are in an ISIS camp.
Every time children experience here,
It's a camp, even on the streets.
ISIS cars are running all the time
with children as goal.
They give them games.
They offer you money,
candy and cell phones.
Something they can not get
of your family.
Join them,
because they have no other choice. Thank you.
I lived in Germany for a year.
Because my English is not bad,
You've been a campaign spokesman.
But the longest time
I am far from Raqqa, -
-Other, I think if we go
You have a house to return.
BERLIN, GERMANY
Germany must strengthen its limits.
Increasing immigration threatens our peace.
The pigs will learn to run.
And they will have a single ticket
Let's go back to the turkey!
Expel them! Expel them! Expel them!
We are trying to be heard
and show the sufferings of the people.
It's the only one
we can do in europe
We try to put pressure on that
refugees and Syrian communities in Berlin.
He does not like Germany,
then you have to travel!
Hello, the organizers!
Why are you here
Turn right
Keep the free page for those who go.
Go! Go! Go!
ALEPPO FIRE
RBSS-HAVEN
A SECRETARY PLACE IN GERMANY
Abu Sheif, can you listen to it?
-Yes, I can hear it.
Hello, honey How are you doing
-You are fine. We missed it
Have a shirt
I hope it warms up.
The house is hot, but looks out.
Affection. Snow
I traveled from Berlin
to the city that I am now.
It's small, but it's temporary.
Then we go on regular occasions.
Have you heard about air strikes yesterday?
Did you see the Aziz video?
Is not Muhammad? Come here
Is Muhammad?
play it
It was home to your uncle Fawzi.
Around your aunt Shukria.
Is it near you?
-Vive at the end of this street.
It is Mamoun's house,
and that was our house.
Is there anybody
-I do not know. Arabawi?
You must verify the names.
- Probably they are the uncles.
The rest is in Damascus
or Saudi Arabia.
Mohamad, you know the family
Moussa al-Akawi or Achawi?
Yes Al-Alchawi. What happens to them?
-They are dead
So far there are 31 martyrs.
Affection.
Death and destruction.
Death persecutes civilians in Raqqa.
Airplanes that support the regime carried out
several attacks on Raqqa, -
what provoked
mass destruction and civilian victims.
More than 30 were killed
and many wounded.
One of the residents said bitterly:
There are a few hundreds of ISIS terrorists
exploit thousands of civilians in the air.
Stop here
The Islamic State assumed responsibility
to kill a Parisian servant.
France shook frightenedly
and I have more waiting soon
- When caliphate soldiers continue
rapists
Go to hell
In France, ISIS took responsibility
by the death of a French officer.
President Hollande called the murder
for an indisputable terrorist act.
Hussam
FOUNDATIONS DO RBSS
ISIS is no longer there
only the problem of Syria.
We saw the danger
arriving to Europe and the United States.
In 18 months, France has
He experienced three deadly attacks.
Attack the unbelievers in your own ways.
France and the Allies should tremble.
50 were killed in the shooting
in the nightclub Press.
It is the worst massive destruction
in the history of the United States.
They are loading
to be inspired by ISIS.
ISIS claims to be behind
a deadly attack in Berlin, -
where a path crawls
a Christmas market and killed at least 12.
For five years, everyone became blind
Look or what's going on in Syria.
Now the whole world is witnessing it,
that happens.
RBSS-HAVEN
A SECRETARY PLACE IN GERMANY
Welcome
My dear Hassan.
How are you doing
Aziz. Give me another master
I'm happy and excited.
I can not remember,
when we met for the last time.
Take a picture
Am on?
You can only see your beard.
It is part of the image.
I'm not an astronomer,
but the sun here looks more white.
We all become whiter.
I always hide.
I do not think the situation is better
in Germany than in Turkey.
There was a demonstration
Yesterday in my city.
There was someone who insulted us,
it's a trembling
It scared me
- Be careful.
Yes, be careful.
-The people can.
We received a lot of attention
from ISIS to the end.
The more pressed they stay,
The more barbarians become.
They are forced into a hook like a cat
and trying to scratch everyone.
The bombs will not do
end of ISIS
ISIS is an idea and will continue,
even if they are grouped.
Today it can be Raqqa,
and tomorrow elsewhere.
So let's update the work, -
-for now we gain experience
fight against extremism.
Just okay
We must move forward and show ourselves
for the international community.
Show the world our faces.
The battle between ISIS and us
it grows every day.
Therefore,
that yes googler Raqqa, -
Not only would he see,
what ISIS wants.
We will find them
Much of what we know
about the cruelty of ISIS in Syria, -
tribes of brave inhabitants
armed with smartphones.
Activists reveal horrors
Behind the ISIS card in its small town.
Professor of mathematics Mohamad Masara
helped create the Raqqa group.
I have to keep alive
And he receives the news, says Mohamad.
It is not enough to reveal
ISIS Crimes
We must also fight
against your ideology.
We learned in Raqqa, -
When a group falls,
another person will take their place.
People want freedom and security, -
-and when they live in a world,
There is neither free nor safe, -
Are they vulnerable to anyone?
group promising prosperity.
It can not be solved by bombs.
Or get rid of ISIS.
We must create a government,
They talk for people.
Thank you.
It is with much humility, -
- I'm getting better
Press Award 2015-
for the brave men and women
Raqqa Be Slammed In Silence.
Thank you.
The members of Raqqa Become.
Slaughtered in Silence is like you.
We love our house and dream
Establish a family and live happily.
The evil that began in Syria,
It will not stop there.
We need the power of good
to face or wrong.
We celebrate this award to our friends,
who offered their lives.
We also celebrate the price for ours
secret campaign heroes
and all the inhabitants of Raqqa. Thank you.
That's enough.
When I came back
to Germany
I discovered,
that there was a new threat to me.
The message stated:
One of the founders of
spy group RBSS-
- He acted two weeks ago
in a television show in Berlin.
The image is represented
Abdulaziz al-Hamza.
I should say
live in germany
So the question is:
- if any
holy warriors in germany
which can kill the founder
of this group of espionage?
Dear Mr. Hamza.
We try to contact you today.
Please, call us
in the previous number
- as soon as possible.
Berlin police
POLITICAL YEAR OF BERLIN
Good morning. My name is Beate.
-Goddag. My name is Aziz.
Are you scared
-me?
I am afraid of the police,
for every time they arrested me,
I was imprisoned and tortured.
Three times with torture and broken power.
You
-Yes.
Your organization is famous.
Understand why ISIS supporters
will you kill him in germany?
It was not the first threat.
I have had threats in all languages.
Via Facebook and Twitter.
What did they write to them?
We will retire the head.
How do you respond to the threat?
Overcome fear
Blood and murder
It's part of my job.
You are in danger,
and we want to protect it.
I understand that,
and renounce that right.
But the right you give up,
It's your right to fight.
It's not just about that
about the police and protection for me.
The friends are dead,
and others are in danger in that
-and I should have
The police protection in Germany?
We understand,
but that's not a good reason.
You do not have to decide today.
Sleeping in it is your choice.
I wish you good luck.
Thank you very much.
With your work and your life.
I have some pictures.
I am looking at the images all the time.
No one knows the images.
Sometimes I think:
Why and not me?
RBSS is like my other family.
Who would think,
that some rabata boys, -
- Forgotten in Syria,
could you do something?
We did
And we are confident that our word-
-It is stronger than your weapons
and his army.
Or we won, -
-or they also beat
move us all.
Raqqa Be Slammed In Silence
still operating inside and outside Syria.
Hamoud, let's take a selfie.
For the devil, I'm filming.
How do you think it's father?
I'm happy
Have you learned to look for it?
-No, not yet.
This is probably enough.
How.
Come on, little friend.
Leave your uncle Hussam.
Your uncle Sarmad.
And for your uncle Aziz, like movies.
What is your name?
-Mohamed.
He already has his name.
After my father, he must rest in peace.